<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Glowify</string>
    <string name="skin_care_activity_title">Skin Care Activity</string>
    <string name="dull_skin_instructions">
    1. Cleanse your face twice daily using a gentle cleanser to remove dirt and impurities.\n\n
    2. Exfoliate regularly to remove dead skin cells and promote cell turnover.\n\n
    3. Use a moisturizer suitable for your skin type to keep your skin hydrated.\n\n
    4. Apply sunscreen daily to protect your skin from harmful UV rays.\n\n
    5. Incorporate antioxidants into your skincare routine to combat free radical damage.\n\n
    6. Stay hydrated by drinking plenty of water throughout the day.\n\n
    7. Get enough sleep to allow your skin to regenerate and repair itself.\n\n
    8. Avoid smoking and limit alcohol intake as they can contribute to dull skin.\n\n
    9. Eat a balanced diet rich in fruits, vegetables, and omega-3 fatty acids to nourish your skin from the inside out.\n
</string>

    <string name="normal_skin_instructions">
    1. Cleanse your face with a gentle cleanser twice daily.\n\n
    2. Moisturize your skin with a lightweight, non-greasy moisturizer.\n\n
    3. Use sunscreen with SPF 30 or higher every morning.\n\n
    4. Exfoliate your skin 1-2 times a week to remove dead skin cells.\n\n
    5. Eat a balanced diet rich in fruits, vegetables, and water.\n\n
    6. Get enough sleep and manage stress levels for healthy skin.\n\n
    7. Avoid using harsh skincare products.\n
</string>

    <string name="dry_skin_instructions">
    1. Use a gentle, creamy cleanser to cleanse your skin without stripping away natural oils.\n\n
    2. Apply a rich, hydrating moisturizer immediately after cleansing to lock in moisture.\n\n
    3. Use a humidifier in dry environments to add moisture to the air.\n\n
    4. Limit exposure to hot water and harsh soaps, as they can further dry out your skin.\n\n
    5. Exfoliate your skin 1-2 times a week to remove dead skin cells and promote cell turnover.\n\n
    6. Avoid prolonged exposure to harsh weather conditions, such as wind and cold.\n\n
    7. Drink plenty of water throughout the day to keep your skin hydrated from the inside out.\n\n
    8. Use a sunscreen with moisturizing properties to protect your skin from UV rays.\n
</string>

    <string name="oily_skin_instructions">
    1. Cleanse your face with a gentle, foaming cleanser twice daily to remove excess oil.\n\n
    2. Use an alcohol-free toner to help control oil production and minimize pores.\n\n
    3. Apply a lightweight, oil-free moisturizer to keep your skin hydrated without clogging pores.\n\n
    4. Use oil-absorbing sheets throughout the day to blot away excess oil.\n\n
    5. Exfoliate your skin 2-3 times a week to remove dead skin cells and prevent breakouts.\n\n
    6. Use a clay mask once a week to deep clean pores and control oiliness.\n\n
    7. Avoid touching your face throughout the day to minimize transferring oil and bacteria.\n\n
    8. Use makeup products labeled as oil_free to prevent pore clogging.\n\n
    9. Limit consumption of greasy and fried foods, as they can contribute to excess oil production.\n\n
    10. Drink plenty of water to stay hydrated and help regulate oil production.\n
</string>

    <string name="sensitive_skin_instructions">
    1. Cleanse your face with a gentle, fragrance-free cleanser twice daily.\n\n
    2. Avoid using products containing alcohol, fragrances, and harsh chemicals.\n\n
    3. Choose skincare products labeled as gentle on acne-prone skin.\n\n
    4. Patch test new products on a small area of your skin before applying them to your face.\n\n
    5. Moisturize your skin with a gentle, non-irritating moisturizer.\n\n
    6. Protect your skin from sun exposure by wearing sunscreen with SPF 30 or higher.\n\n
    7. Avoid hot water and long showers, as they can strip your skin of its natural oils.\n\n
    8. Limit exposure to extreme temperatures and harsh weather conditions.\n\n
    9. Be cautious with exfoliation and limit it to once a week with a gentle scrub.\n\n
    10. Consult a dermatologist if you experience persistent skin irritation or reactions.\n
</string>

    <string name="combination_skin_instructions">
    1. Cleanse your face with a gentle, pH-balanced cleanser twice daily.\n\n
    2. Use a lightweight moisturizer on dry areas and a mattifying moisturizer on oily areas.\n\n
    3. Apply sunscreen with SPF 30 or higher to protect your skin from sun damage.\n\n
    4. Use a targeted treatment for acne-prone areas, if necessary.\n\n
    5. Exfoliate your skin 2-3 times a week to remove dead skin cells.\n\n
    6. Avoid using harsh products that can strip your skin of its natural oils.\n\n
    7. Use a hydrating mask on dry areas and a clay mask on oily areas.\n\n
    8. Keep your skincare routine simple and avoid using too many products.\n\n
    9. Stay hydrated by drinking plenty of water throughout the day.\n\n
    10. Consult a dermatologist if you experience persistent skin issues.\n
</string>

    <string name="acne_prone_skin_instructions">
    1. Cleanse your face with a gentle, acne-friendly cleanser twice daily.\n\n
    2. Use products containing salicylic acid or aloe vera to help treat and prevent acne.\n\n
    3. Avoid touching or picking at your acne to prevent further irritation and scarring.\n\n
    4. Moisturize your skin with a lightweight, oil-free moisturizer.\n\n
    5. Apply sunscreen with SPF 30 or higher to protect your skin from sun damage.\n\n
    6. Use a clay mask once a week to help absorb excess oil and unclog pores.\n\n
    7. Avoid using heavy makeup and opt for acne-safe or oil-free formulas.\n\n
    8. Wash your pillowcases and face towels regularly to prevent bacteria buildup.\n\n
    9. Maintain a healthy diet rich in fruits, vegetables, and whole grains.\n\n
    10. Consult a dermatologist for personalized treatment options if acne persists.\n
</string>

    <string name="sun_damaged_skin_instructions">
    1. Protect your skin from further sun damage by wearing sunscreen with SPF 30 or higher daily.\n\n
    2. Use products containing antioxidants like vitamin C and E to repair and protect your skin.\n\n
    3. Apply a moisturizer with hyaluronic acid to help hydrate and plump up sun-damaged skin.\n\n
    4. Use a gentle scrub to remove dead skin cells and promote skin renewal.\n\n
    5. Consider using products with retinoids to stimulate collagen production and improve skin texture.\n\n
    6. Avoid prolonged sun exposure, especially during peak hours, and wear protective clothing and hats.\n\n
    7. Drink plenty of water to keep your skin hydrated from the inside out.\n\n
    8. Consult a dermatologist for personalized treatment options if you experience severe sun damage.\n
</string>


</resources>